[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING]
Django, Django. Look, it's Gabo.
Great timing!
- [GUNSHOT]
- Gabo, your father got shot!
Pa!
Django, what if Gabo finds out
about this?
Then good!
At least he'll know what happens
if he dares cross me again.
Who shot my father?
If I found out who ordered
that demolition,
I'll make that person pay!
Including their family!
Ginintuang Lupa
is all over the news!
I won't stop until every
last one of them is gone.
Doc, how is the patient doing?
We need to operate
on him right away.
We don't have anything saved up.
What are we going to do?
I'll take care of everything.
I'll do whatever it takes
to save Papa.
We won't do anything
wrong just to save Papa's life.
If we have to beg, we will.
As long as my father
gets his surgery.
- Man...
- Bummer...
We're getting nowhere!
What else are we supposed to do?
Let's just think of other ways
we could help Gabo.
I know a way! I'm sure
we'll hit jackpot!
Maybe we could get ourselves
a car while we're at it!
- [IN UNISON] Where?!
- Don't worry!
We know the way to go
so if I were you,
just follow us. Let's go!
And throw those away.
- [WATER SPLASHING]
- [TEKLA] Let's move.
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING]
- Hey there, handsome!
- Come on in!
- Welcome!
- Go on in!
You know what, Paquito,
we still got it.
Why would we loose our touch?
We've always been doing this.
Also, Romy, call Tuklaw.
Tell him to hand over the money
we worked hard for.
Paquito! Did you just arrive?
So that's why.
- What are you talking about?
- Oh, you missed out on a lot!
Things just kept on happening!
It's like a melodrama.
It had me gasping for air!
Oh, please.
You're just asthmatic!
What even happened?
Oh, Paquito.
That son of yours stirred up
some trouble again!
Nothing new there.
I'm already used to him
brawling with someone.
This time he got beaten
to a pulp!
Django didn't stand a chance
against Gabo!
Mind you, he just got out
from prison.
Huh? Romy, let's go.
Huh?
Not gonna join us for a drink?
[TEKLA] Just where on earth
are you taking us?
[BINOY] It's over here!
I'm telling you guys,
we'll strike it big here!
- Especially Gabo!
- That's right! [GIGGLES]
Hey, is this illegal?
Watch it. I know
how you guys are.
He just got out of prison,
he can't get mixed up
with iffy things.
It's not illegal!
We'll earn a lot from this
as long as we're good
with our words
and we're generous.
- Exactly, exactly.
- Yeah!
What will our jobs be anyway?
A male stripper at a gay bar!
This is where rich
gay people go!
- [BINOY] Right!
- Come on!
Let's just go. I got you guys!
Follow my lead.
- [BINOY] Let's go!
- [TOLITS] Let's!
[TEKLA] Are we really
gonna listen to those two?
[TOLITS] Sir, we'll just inquire
inside. I'm with them.
[OLGA] It's so stuffy
in here!
You're all way too big!
How are you gonna sell tonight?
We have so many customers
today, too!
Remember, we have a big night!
If I lose customers
because of all of you
you'll be fired!
Shake those hips! Come on!
[CLUB MUSIC CONTINUES]
Table for ten?
Oh, no. We're not guests.
- We're here to apply.
- For what position?
- As male strippers.
- Male stripper?
Oh, perfect! We need a lot
because it's a big night!
- Come! I'll get you to Madam.
- [BINOY CHEERING]
[TOLITS] Let's go.
[STAFF] Madam!
[STAFF] Madam, we got
applicants! They're all hunks!
[OLGA] You startled me!
Oh, perfect! We have
a big night today!
Which one of you is applying
for the position?
- You?
- Me too!
- You too?
- Me three!
Let me take a look.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [TOLITS LAUGHING]
- Delicious! [GIGGLING]
- You're good to go.
- Alright!
- And you? Open it up.
- Oh.
- Not that! This one!
- Oops!
You're doing too much.
- Look at those abs!
- I got a four pack hehe.
You're hired!
Me too! My hips don't lie!
[LAUGHING MOCKINGLY]
Pack it up. You'll ruin
my business!
Do you see yourself?
You look way too healthy!
- Don't mind it, bro.
- Get out!
- And you two?
- Oh... us?
Do you have spots left
for uh... waiters?
You know, your timing
is impeccable.
It's our big night! We have
a lot of customers.
And we'll also have
lots of dishes to wash.
Okay? I'll leave you to it!
- And you?
- Oh, me?
- What are you applying for?
- I can do anything!
I can be a bartender
or a cashier!
A cashier?
With how you look,
I don't trust you.
You'll work in the kitchen,
'kay?
- Okay! I can do that.
- [OLGA CLEARS THROAT]
Uh, and you? Are you
applying too?
Well, if you're okay with me.
Come closer. Don't go farther!
Come closer
and let me sniff you.
- [LAUGHTER]
- Oh, you. It's just a sniff!
Come closer! Why are you
stepping back? Come on!
Let me see it.
I'll just take a look!
- Looks like Madam is lively.
- [GABO CHUCKLES]
I'm not applying here
as a male stripper...
What are you here
for then?!
I'd like to apply as a bouncer,
if it's possible.
I'm good at fighting.
I can defend you.
Oh, we can't do that.
That's not allowed here.
An escort!
- That okay?
- Gabo, an escort is good!
You'll earn a lot. You'll afford
the operation for Sir Rudy!
[OLGA] Well then,
you good with it?
You're good to go!
- [OLGA] All good?
- [STUTTERING] S-- sure, uh...
- I'll be an escort.
- Okay!
- Then, I'll leave them to you.
- Let's go then.
- Thank you so much!
- Ma'am, thank you!
[OLGA] It's nothing.
Hey, mister.
[SNIFFS] You're such a hottie!
Django!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Pa, what's the matter?
Did Gabo beat you up?
That bastard just got out
of prison
and he already messed with you?!
Boss Paquito is here.
That's right, Pa.
I challenged him
when I found out that...
he came back to Ginintuang Lupa.
And you let yourself
get beaten up by him?!
Gabo not only beat Django up
he wrecked havoc here
and ruined our businesses!
You can't just blatantly
disrespect
the king of Ginintuang Lupa!
Gather our men!
This very night,
we'll knock Gabo down
and spare not one member
of his clan!
[GUNS COCKING]
Let's go.
Hold your horses!
[IBYANG] Calm down, will you?
If we head over there right now,
it'll be useless
because I'm certain
he won't be there.
Rudy got rushed to the hospital.
Why? You already fought back?
[IBYANG] Someone already
shot him earlier
during the demolition.
Paquito, all of you.
You all know that Gabo
was imprisoned for eight years.
We don't know what kind of hell
he went through in there
to turn him into some demon.
She's right, Boss Paquito.
It's dangerous if we rush
there right now.
Papa's already here.
There's so many of us!
What are you so afraid of?!
I want to get back
on that demon too!
But our heads aren't just
for decoration!
Let's prepare for this!
We can't just strike blindly.
We'll lose for sure!
Ibyang's got a point, Pa.
There's no need to rush.
There's a right moment
to kill Gabo.
Let's think of a plan first.
What's important...
is that we got back at him,
even if it's just a little.
What do you mean?
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
I shot Rudy.
It was you?!
[DJANGO] That's right.
- Right on the chest!
- [SINISTER LAUGHTER]
And I'm pretty sure
that a day or two from now,
he'll be rotting away
in a coffin!
[SINISTER LAUGHTER]
That's my boy!
Clever! If you can't
get the son,
strike his father!
[SINISTER LAUGHTER]
That's not all, Pa!
After they mourn Rudy's death,
they'll mourn Gabo next!
[SINISTER LAUGHTER]
So it was you, huh?!
Nicely done!
[SINISTER LAUGHTER CONTINUES]
This is what
male strippers wear.
- There. Okay.
- This is their outfit.
Go get changed
because tonight's a big night.
We have a lot of customers.
Wait, what about the escort?
Uh...
I didn't bring
an extra set of clothes.
Huh? Wait, let me see you.
This will work.
Make sure to do your best
because tonight's a big night.
Our regular, Mama Franny,
is coming.
The waiters and dishwashers,
come with me.
Hey.
- [TOLITS] Why?
- You take care of Gabo.
[TOLITS] Yeah, just start
washing there.
Scrub out the grease!
We'll handle this!
I hope...
I get paid a big amount
so my dad can have
his surgery.
Uhh, Gabo, don't worry.
We'll give all our earnings
to you,
so Sir Rudy can have
his surgery.
And make sure
to give it your all!
Keep flattering the customers,
so they give you tips, alright?
And give them everything
they want.
[STAFF] Come here.
The dishwasher works here.
Don't break anything.
Handle the glasses
and plates carefully.
As for the waiters...
It's a big night,
so go get changed.
Work properly.
Stay here on the left.
A lot of my regular customers
are coming.
So you get a lot of tips!
What's with him? I said
I wanted to be the cashier!
- [DABOY] What should we do?
- Put these on.
- Wear these!
- Fine.
Clean up the mess,
and throw it in the trash.
- [MAN] Work properly!
- I wanted to be a cashier!
I don't even know
how to wash dishes,
- but they put me here.
- Because you keep eating!
I love dancing!
I dreamed of becoming
a male stripper!
What?
[TEKLA LAUGHING]
Why are you laughing?
You want to be a male stripper?
- You? Are you serious?
- Yeah!
My gosh! If you dance there,
you might break the stage.
Or the customers
might start throwing up.
[TEKLA LAUGHING]
- Wow. Why?
- Male stripper...
I can shake my hips!
- I'm good at it!
- That's it!
Ohh, you're right!
I have an idea.
Why don't you go outside,
and then surprise them?
- Hurry!
- That's a great idea.
- You sure?
- Yeah!
- You're not joking?
- I'm not!
Go on, you're just taking up
space here.
You know, Tekla, I always
wanted to become a dancer.
You might fall in love with me
if I shake my hips like this.
No, I'm going to close my eyes.
- Go there, go.
- Alright, you take care here.
Tekla! You take care of that!
[TEKLA SIGHS DEEPLY]
[SCREAMING EXCITEDLY]
Let's go!
- Ta-da!
- Mama, big night!
Of course! That's why
I brought you to my territory.
Let's get inside!
We might run out of boys!
Don't worry, girls.
I'm friends with the manager.
And I made sure the best
of the best is reserved for us!
- Let's go!
- Oh, I love that!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[FRANNY] Hello, boys.
Hello, hello.
Welcome to my place to be!
[STAFF] Mama Franny!
You've arrived!
Of course!
I know you have a big night!
We have a lot of new ones today.
You're sure there are a lot
of fresh ones?
[ERIKA] Maybe these are
just boys you got bored of.
- Mm-hmm!
- That's not true.
He's very handsome.
I think we're going home
very happy, Mama!
- Perfect! Lead the way!
- [STAFF] This way.
[TONET] Let's go!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- [OLGA] Mama Franny!
- Sister!
[OLGA] Long time no see!
[SMACKS]
Of course, when you invite me,
I'm always present,
especially with tonight's
big night!
Of course, you're exactly
who we need!
- You know that!
- Where do we sit?
- Here.
- Perfect.
- You can clearly see them.
- Let's sit, girls.
[BINOY] Do it slowly at first.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
It's slow, it's a love song!
- [TOLITS] It's not hip-hop?
- [BINOY] It's not hip-hop!
You think we'll wear
these shorts if it's hip-hop?
Do it slowly,
then point at our customers.
Keep pointing at them.
[FRANNY] Sister,
before we order,
call on the boys
so we can start choosing.
- That's right!
- Exactly!
Go on, call them.
Don't point a gun at them!
Just point!
[STAFF] Where are
the male strippers?
Hey, Madam Olga's calling
for you.
What are you doing there?
Hurry up, and go out!
Gabo, let's go.
Mama Franny is here.
You'll earn big tonight!
Let's go!
These male strippers
are so slow!
Gabo, you can do it!
Be nice!
Give in to what they want!
- Nice.
- Again, slow.
And then they like it
when we do this.
What's this?
- The chicken comb!
- The chicken comb?
Go like this.
- [OLGA] How are you?
- [FRANNY] I'm fine!
[OLGA] I thought
you had replaced us!
[FRANNY] You know
when I get possessed,
- I always come here.
- [LAUGHING]
- [STAFF] Here they are!
- [FRANNY] Uh.
Oh. Uh, sorry, sir.
- There! Oh, what's that? Ugh.
- Oh, oh!
Those moves are disgusting!
I'm suddenly craving for bopis.
[LAUGHING]
[OLGA] You, guys, really!
- [FRANNY] Oh!
- [OLGA] Up to your taste?
Sister! This--
This long haired guy.
He's mine.
- But he's mine too.
- But I want him too!
- I'm the first one who saw him!
- Give him to us!
Whose is he? Whose is he?
- Fine, yours.
- [OLGA] Wait.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Come here, I'll introduce you!
This is Mama Franny.
He's our big time customer!
- [FRANNY] Mm-hmm.
- Everyone who sits there
doesn't go home empty-handed!
He's very kind and generous.
[FRANNY] Aw, thank you, sister!
- I'll bring him home.
- Later.
[ERIKA] It's like his eyes
are doing the talking.
This is it.
[FRANNY CLEARS THROAT]
Have a seat!
- What the-- Oh my god!
- [TONET] He's handsome!
- Oh my!
- [TONET] So handsome!
My girls are so hungry,
especially this guy.
Waiter!
- Hurry!
- Here's the menu.
- No need for the menu.
- We'll have the usual!
- They already know it!
- Tell the cook
that Mama Franny is here.
Go on, go on.
- [FRANNY] Thank you!
- Go.
- [OLGA] You take care of him.
- Yes, of course!
- Thank you!
- [OLGA] Bye!
- Bye, sister!
- [TONET] He's so handsome!
- Shh!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRESS RUSTLES]
[HANGER RATTLES]
[EXHALES]
[GASPS]
[SQUEALING]
- [ERIKA] Ooh!
- [FRANNY] Shh! Uh...
[HIGH-PITCHED] Excuse me,
what's your name?
Why are you speaking like that?
- [GABO] I-It's Gabriel.
- Gabriel!
Oh my gosh, it's like the angel!
- His name is so innocent!
- And he looks like a Gabriel!
I love it!
But...
T-They call me Gabo
in my neighborhood.
- Gabo! That's so masculine!
- [ERIKA] I think I prefer Gabo
because it sounds like
you're ready for battle.
- Gabo sounds rough!
- So masculine!
- [TONET] Yes!
- [FRANNY] And...
Where are you from, Gabo?
I'm from Tondo.
- Ah!
[TONET] Men from Tondo
are really handsome!
[ERIKA] They have a selection!
Uh, Gabo, why are you working
in a place like this?
Because...
My father is in the hospital.
He needs to undergo surgery
because he was shot.
Gabo, all of you here
have needs.
It's like everyone
who works here has a problem.
- I know, right?
- But it is true.
This is the list
of what I need to buy
for him to have surgery.
- Oh, wow.
- Maybe you can help me.
He thinks you're a pharmacy!
No, he thinks you're from DSWD!
[ERIKA] He even brought
the prescription!
But he's incredible.
He has props!
Uh, you know, Gabo,
don't worry.
I give big tips.
You might reach your quota.
[TONET] Let's have that later.
The night is still young.
What I'm saying is true.
I'm only here because
my father is in the hospital.
- Maybe you can help me.
- [FRANNY] Shh!
Let's have that later. What
I'm telling you is also true.
I give big tips!
- [TONET] Yeah!
- Meanwhile, let's have fun!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[ERIKA] Uh, Gabo,
keep that for now.
Listen, um...
Do you like...
- ...rubber shoes?
- He's putting out an offer!
I don't like rubber shoes.
Oh, sorry, he doesn't like it!
That's an X for you!
[LAUGHING]
[TONET] Gabo, do you have
a cellphone?
[SQUEALS]
I do, but...
It's old, but it works fine.
Okay, he doesn't want
a cellphone.
He wants something simple.
He's not techie.
Ah, Gabo,
do you want a motorcycle?
Huh? You're going all out?
- You're really giving him one?
- Of course!
No thanks.
I'm good with walking.
- He's picky.
- What a shame. Maybe he's shy.
He can provide for your needs.
while he only rented.
What's with you?!
You might say that's true.
- But there is a chance.
- [LAUGHING]
No thanks.
I'm okay.
- He's hard to get.
- [MAN] And now, please welcome,
our new dancers,
Tolits and Binoy!
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
Here they are, Mama!
[SLAPS STAGE]
Woo!
- Woo!
- Wow! Woo! Woo!
[CROWD CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
Look at that guy!
His body's so beautiful!
- [FRANNY] The one on the left?
- [TONET] Him!
His body may be great,
but look at his face.
I'll remove his head
like a shrimp.
- His face is long?
- It's long.
But look at the other one.
He's cute, but...
- He's like a wrestler.
- [FRANNY] Yeah.
He moves so smoothly.
[FRANNY] If I see him
on the streets,
I'll hide my bag.
He looks like a thief!
- He looks like a mugger!
- [TONET] Don't worry.
They're nice people.
- Huh?
- [GABO] They're my friends.
They're only working here
to help me.
[FRANNY] Oh, they're friends.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Well, they're surprisingly good
at dancing!
[ERIKA] Look at their skin.
Kayumanggi na liga.
In English, dirty brown.
[LAUGHING]
[MAN] And now, with a very
special guest dancer,
Daboy!
- [TONET] Oh! Oh! Oh my god!
- [FRANNY] Oh! Oh my gosh!
[CROWD CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[TONET] What is that?!
What kind of dancer is that?!
He even has a lot
of stretch marks!
[ERIKA] Look, he has wings!
If he becomes a manananggal,
with his weight,
his insides will fall!
[LAUGHING]
[TONET] Oh my god.
His tummy's cute!
He's like a living gelatin!
[LAUGHING]
[FRANNY] Olga's so funny.
She literally made it
into a big night!
[LAUGHING]
This is so funny.
He's heavier than the stage!
If he doesn't have makeup,
we look alike!
[FRANNY] This is just so funny.
What's with Olga? Are there
no more male strippers?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi, miss.
You're the new
dishwasher, right?
[TEKLA INHALES SHARPLY]
Yes, and?
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- Yes, I do have one!
It's Gabo, he's actually
entertaining people outside.
[LAUGHTER]
[FRANNY] Anyway...
Gabo.
Wow, his muscles are huge!
[TONET] Really? Are those real?
Wow! I'm impressed!
[ERIKA] It feels so good to
touch him... he's not that thin.
[FRANNY] See? Guys...
[TONET] It's fine.
Let's just feel his legs.
[FRANNY] That's enough.
He doesn't want
anyone else touching him.
He only wants me.
You know what, Gabo...
Uh...
How much are you?
I'm going to take
you out, c'mon, let's go!
[TONET] Come on, Gabo.
You should come with us.
This show is boring.
[ERIKA] Just tell us your price.
- Oh!
I'm not that kind of person.
Oh, c'mon.
Don't be shy.
I'll take care
of whatever you need.
- [TONET] Gabo...
- You just need
to come with me.
[TONET] C'mon,
pull him a little closer.
Get a feel of his chest,
Franny.
Don't be shy.
[MAN 1] Being a dishwasher
doesn't suit you.
Being my girlfriend
suits you more.
- [PLATE CLATTERS]
- No, my girlfriend.
[CHUCKLES]
Yuck! Yuck! Yuck!
- What do you mean by "yuck"?
- Let me go!
[KICKS LANDING]
What did you expect, huh?!
Just because I'm a woman,
you'd think I'd back down?!
- I'm from Tondo!
- [POTS CLATTERING]
I won't back down
from you, no way!
Don't worry, Gabo.
I'll take care...
- There we go! That's it.
- of you...
- [BONES CRUNCHING]
- [SCREAMING] Aah!
- You too!
- [BLOWS, KICKS LANDING]
That's enough, Gabo!
[MAN 1] Miss! Miss! Miss!
- [BLOWS, KICKS LANDING]
- [SCREAMING] Aah!
[SCREAMING]
What?!
[JOYCE] What
have you done, Gabo?!
- These people are harassing me!
- [JOYCE] What did they do?!
[YELLS] I'm just being friendly,
but instead, he beat me up!
- Get him out of here!
- Look at what you've done!
I'll sue you!
I don't care if you sue me!
[JOYCE] What have you done?!
I can buy you!
I can buy this club!
I'm going to sue you all!
[JOYCE] Get out of here, now!
Just go!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- [JOYCE] I'm so sorry!
- [TEKLA] Let's go!
Get out of here, now! Get out!
- [CRYING]
- I'm so sorry! I'm sorry!
- I just got a facial!
- [JOYCE] I'm so sorry!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
You need to pay for what
you've done to my face!
What happened, Gabo?!
Why did you beat up those gays?
We were surprised!
We were dancing,
and then you suddenly attacked
the people at your table!
We were trying to help you,
and this is how you'll act.
We were doing a good job!
The pay was actually good!
I'm being groped
by gay men!
And then they still want
to get what they want!
I told you, didn't I?
You should be generous.
You should have just given in!
That's not how Gabo is!
C'mon, guys,
if Gabo is against it,
then he really won't do it!
[TEKLA] Well, what
are we going to do now?
It's so hard to help you, Gabo.
We tried helping you, but we all
ended up in a bad spot.
Did I ask for your help, huh?
Even if you don't help me,
I can take care of myself!
- Wow...
- Gabo!
Gabo!
What will we do now?
Gabo got mad at us.
This is your fault!
Your comments were too much!
What?
Daboy was telling the truth.
All we did was help and look
at where it got us!
We're helping Gabo so
Rudy can afford his surgery!
Why can't you just try
to understand him?
Isn't he going
through something?!
How about you try being
in his situation!
[BONG] That's enough.
All I'm worried about now
is where will Gabo go?
Let's just wait for him at home.
He'll be there for sure.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN CLICKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
I know who you are.
I've seen your faces
when I was in jail.
We've been keeping
an eye on you for a long time.
What do you need from me?
You'll find out later.
[GRUNTS] Argh!
[GROANS] Ahh...
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS] Ahh...
[GROANS] Ahh..
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS] Ahh...
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[SIGHS]
Where am I?
Who are you?
What do you need from me?!
Gabo!
Calm down.
[GRUNTS]
Gabo! Gabo!
[LAWIN] Calm down.
Who are you?
You'll find out soon.
- [GROANS] Argh!
- [GUN CLATTERS]
[GRUNTS] Argh!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- Lie down!
What do you need from me?
[LAWIN] Gabo! Wait!
You won't talk?!
- Huh?
- Calm down! Calm down!
You don't understand!
Hold on.
[INTENSE ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
Gabo!
Tatang?
[INTENSE ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INTENSE ROCK MUSIC
CONTINUES, FADES]
We have to make no mistakes
on our report later.
Someone will sit in
on our briefing.
- Who?
- Hi, guys!
It's like you've seen
a ghost?
I'm here.
Many of them are brave fighters,
but very few of them
have a true warrior's heart.
If you spot anyone,
let me know immediately.
So I can inspect them.
The chaos around is rampant.
And sometimes,
the criminals are already
working with those in power.
We will lose a lot
if we lose Ginintuang Lupa.
I know we have an agreement
with the police,
but I hope they don't fool us.
- Even if they're the police,
- [GUN COCKS]
I won't let them get away.
That's why the Anino is here,
to help clean
up our country.
We need someone
who is wholehearted.
Good fighter, fearless,
and with integrity.
We have seen your skill,
strength, and excellence.
We need you, Gabo.